Knight Rider 2000 is a action, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Alan J. Levi.
In the future, guns are banned and criminals are frozen
for the duration of their sentences.
A recent spate of killings involving handguns brings Michael Knight back to fight for justice, but
he insists of the help of KITT, his artificially-intelligent car from decades ago.
The only problem is that KITT has been deactivated.
Michael Knight, played by David Hasselhoff.
Devon Miles, played by Edward Mulhare.
Officer Shawn McCormick, played by Susan Norman.
Russell Maddock / Voice of K.I.T.T., played by Carmen Argenziano.
Thomas J. Watts, played by Mitch Pileggi.
Officer Kurt Miller, played by Eugene Clark.
Knight Rider 2000 is a 1991 American made-for-television science fiction
action film based on the 1982–1986 television series Knight Rider.
The film explores themes of man vs machine,
government, police, cryogenics, robot.
The tone is thought_provoking.